Guide to the Nathan Fawcett papers, 1983-1999.
Fawcett, Nathan papers, 1983-1999.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Nathan Fawcett papers, 1983-1999.
4-12-3183.
Nathan Fawcett.
7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, minutes, reports, reviews, financial documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Includes correspondence, minutes, reports and subject files pertaining to Fawcett's tenure as Director of the Statutory Finance and Business Office and Assistant to the President and SUNY affairs.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Special Assistant to the Provost for State-Related Issues, formally the Assistant to the President (beginning in 1987), and Director of the Statutory Finance and Business Office (beginning in 1983).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, minutes, reports and subject files pertaining to Fawcett's tenure as Director of the Statutory Finance and Business Office and Assistant to the President and SUNY Affairs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Fawcett, Nathan.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Finance.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Planning.; Cornell University. Assistant to the President.; Cornell University. Statutory Finance and Business Office.; University of the State of New York.
Subjects:
Federal aid to higher education.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Nathan Fawcett Papers
  - Academic Programs Registration, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accreditation Review, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Charge, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adm. Computing, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ag & Life Sciences - Swine Barn, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ag & Life Sciences Contract, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Indian Program, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Audit State Comptroller, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bailey Hortorium, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Barton Hall (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biological Sciences Division, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biological & Plant Science Res. Building, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biotechnology Building (Accounting Between State & Endowed) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bonding Cap Legislation, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boyce Thompson Institute Roof Replacement, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Capital Rehabilitation Budget Requests, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rehabilitation Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Final State Budget, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Final State Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Capital Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Capital Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Statutory Deans' Meeting Minutes, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Final Budget Request, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bundy Aid, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CALS - misc., correspondence, planning, 1987-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Capital Campaign, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Capital Planning, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Capital Projects, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Center for the Environment (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Child Care Center (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CIT, Capital Equipment Proposal (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Classroom Scheduling Project System, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Computing Charges, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Computing & Network Security, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Comstock Addition to ACAD II (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cooke Analysis (Trends: employees at Cornell), 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cooperative Extension, Area Specialists, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cooperative Extension Initiatives, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Outreach Council (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cost Accounting Review Group (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Costing Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Debt Service Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Distance Learning (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - NYS Budget - Misc. Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Early Retirement Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Economic Development Projects, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Economic Depts., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Economic Impact Analysis, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Economic Status Stat. Facility Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Environmental Health, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Equipment Inventory Control Tag - old correspondence (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Experimental Animal Facility - Baker, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Numbers, 1991-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Federal Funds Study Group, 1988-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Financial Aid Study Group, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Food Science Lab, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Functional Report Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Office - Misc. Correspondence, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Research Initiatives, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Student Stipends, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Tuition Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Greenhouse Project (CALS), 1988-1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Higher Education Studies & Reports (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Human Ecology Master Plan, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Human Ecology - Misc. Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ILR - Misc. Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Information Technologies - Financial Restructure, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Instructional Computing - correspondence, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Insurance Rates correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Library Automation, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Libraries/Misc. Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Long Island Horticultural Research Lab, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Maintenance Correspondence, General, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Maintenance Conversion Project, 1972-1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Mann Library Loading Dock Relocation (file never came), 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mann Library - old correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mann Library - old back up material, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Media Services Merger (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Materials Management, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Naming of Statutory Buildings (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NASULGC - Misc., 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Naval Research Audit Reports, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New York Bond Act Correspondence, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Northeast Dairy - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NYS - Agency Contracts, 1989-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NYS Contracts - Misc. Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ornithology - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Peer Analysis - Old Material, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pesticide Storage Facilities, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Planning/Long Range, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Plant Science Greenhouse General, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Plantations - Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Policies & Procedures - General on Steering Group, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Planning & Wage Issues, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Project 2000 - Backup and Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Public Works Contracts, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Racing & Wagering Board Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate Transactions, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Resource Allocation Task File, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Project Documents-correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Responsibility Center Overview (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Statutory Faculty Salaries - Misc. Correspondence & Reports, 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Savage Hall General Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Sea Grant Correspondence, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Special Fund Estimates Closeout Certifications, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs - Accounts & Correspondence, 1987-1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Space Issues - General Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Small Animal Holding Facility, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - State Dept. of Social Services Correspondence & Contracts, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - State Health Dept. - Breast Research Correspondence, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Statutory Deans - cost impact meeting back-up, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - State Facilities/Misc., 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - State Facilities/Policies Procedures - Old Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Statutory College Income Fund Correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - State Surge Facility, 1988-1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Study Abroad Implementation Plan, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - SUNY Environmental Audit, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - SUNY Card, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - SUCF Bonding (3 files), 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Strategic Planning Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Ethics & Internal Control, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - SUNY Fin. Audit Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Human Resource Mgmt Systems (HRMS), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - SUNY Report: "On Working Group on Campus Customers of SUNY System", 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Student Computing Access Program, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Surge I Facility, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tuition - General Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Theory Center Misc. Correspondence - 6 Folders, 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Underrepresented Minority Faculty, 1989-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Underrepresented Minority Students, 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Veterinary Medicine Master Plan, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Vet Medicine/Facilities Misc., incl. Schurm Hall, environmental health issues, 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Vet Diagnostic Lab Facility (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - University Relations - Media Services (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Utilities - rates, surveys, 1988-1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)